Hey there.How are you doing?
Hey there. 你好吗?
Hi Pam.You know George,don't you?
Hi Pam. 你认识George, 对吗?
Sure.Hi.
当然. 你好.
Where are you going?
你去哪里呀?
Jarmusch gave me the afternoon off.
Jarmusch下午给我放假.
We were working until 2a.m.last night.
昨晚我们一直工作到凌晨两点.
You weren't cooking,were you?
你们不是在烧菜吧?
No.We were finishing the new menu.
No. 我们在拟定新菜单.
Jarmusch has changed everything.Now it's classic cuisine.
Jarmusch把什么都改变了. 现在是经典菜品.
We've been planning it for weeks.
我们已经为此准备了好几个星期了.
It sounds like a lot of work.
听起来很大的工作量.
It's been endless.
真是没完没了.
And Jarmusch has been driving me crazy.
Jarmusch要把我逼疯了.
Jarmusch is crazy.
Jarmusch真是疯了.
Do you have to show the new menu to anyone?
你们必须把新菜单给饭店的其他人看吗?
Oh yeah.
Jarmusch was showing it to Simon and Nino when they left.
Jarmusch正在给Simon和Nino看呢,在我离开的时候.
Sharon asked for it,too.
Sharon也要求要看.
Everyone has their two cents to put in.
每个人都想发表自己的见解.
So,who was cooking while you were planning?
那么, 你们在拟菜单的时候谁在做饭呢?
Another cook!
另一个厨师!
We were just going to lunch.
我们正准备去吃午餐.
Would you like to join us?
你愿意和我们一块儿去吗?
Thanks,but the last thing I want to do is look at a menu.
谢谢, 我现在最不愿意的事情就是看菜单了.